PAK HIN EDEN WONG

28 Empress Ave, Toronto, Ontario, M2N 6Z7 | (437)981-9858 | wedenpakhin@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Multi-talented Front Desk Supervisor adept at managing guest expectations, hotel reputation and business needs. Effective multitasker and clear communicator with 5 years in the hospitality industry. Described as an outgoing, well-organised and motivated team player who is always willing to help and learning new skills. Have been working in hospitality and customer service for the past 5 years, and worked in several 5 stars hotels in Hong Kong. Eden is now in Toronto, ON, and continues his study. Meanwhile, he is seeking a part time job related to customer service to obtain more experience.

SKILLS

- Team Building and Supervision
- Multitasking and Organization
- Decision Making
- Relationship Building
- Team Leadership
- Customer Service
- Hotel Opera System
- Handling Customer Complaints
- Handling Complaints

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

The SoHo Hotel and Residences - Guest Service Representative

October 2022 - present

- Acts as the first point of contact for guests and visitors in a busy environment
- Promptly checks-in/checks-out guests
- Responds to inquiries and requests in-person, through email, and phone calls
- Creates, updates, and manages reservations on Opera
- Processes payments, deposits, and refunds; maintains accurate account balances
- Manages guest and staff access keys
- Coordinates with housekeeping and other departments
- Accepts and distributes checked items, luggage, mail, and packages
- Maintains lobby cleanliness and ensures it is presentable
- Assists with various other matters as required

WM Hotel, Hong Kong - Front Desk Supervisor

December 2021 - August 2022

- Lead and perform all front desk duties including check-ins, checkouts, reservations, guest phone messages and special request
- Ensure that all front office and guest services team members receive adequate training in all
- Trained new staff on correct procedures, compliance requirements and performance strategies.
- Oversaw front desk operations with eye for hotel reputation, staff productivity and operational efficiency.

Harbour Grand Hong Kong, Hong Kong — Assistant Front Desk Supervisor

December 2020 - December 2021

- Manage the activities of a Front Office team ensuring that guests receive prompt, professional attention and personal recognition
- Handle emergency cases in accordance with hotel group policy and procedures.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- Carried out day-day-day duties accurately and efficiently.

Rosedale Hotel Hong Kong, Hong Kong - Senior Front Desk Officer

August 2017 - December 2020

- Assisting front office operations and maintaining good relationship with the guests
- Handle check in and out procedures in the reception for the guests
- Performed duties in accordance with applicable standards, policies and regulatory guidelines to promote safe working environment.

EDUCATION

- Software Engineering Technician Postgraduate program –
 Centennial College | December 2023 | Grade: GPA 4.07
- Bsc(Hons)International Tourism and Hospitality Management -University of Sunderland | December 2015
- High Diploma in Hospitality And Tourism Management Compass College- AHLA | September 2014